digitalmusicnews.com 2017-09-02

# Privacy Policy | Digital Music News

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the [http://www.digitalmusicnews.com](http://www.digitalmusicnews.com/) and Digital Music News and governs data collection and usage.  For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Digital Music News include http://www.digitalmusicnews.com and DMN. The DMN website is a News and information site. By using the DMN website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us at support@digitalmusicnews.com.

**Safe Harbor Certification**

The United States Department of Commerce and the European Commission have agreed on a set of data protection principles and frequently asked questions (the “Safe Harbor Principles”) to enable U.S. companies to satisfy the EU law requirement that personal information transferred from the EU to the United States be adequately protected. Consistent with its pledge to protect personal privacy, DMN complies with the Safe Harbor Principles.

Additional information about the Safe Harbor program is available at the U.S. Department of Commerce’s website at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

DMN may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. DMN may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and buying habits. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by DMN. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the DMN website. DMN encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from DMN so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. DMN is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the DMN website.

**Use of your Personal Information**

DMN collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

DMN may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from DMN and its affiliates. DMN may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

DMN may sell, rent, or lease customer information to third parties for the following reasons:

Optional surveying only on for industry specific data.

DMN may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to DMN, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

DMN may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within DMN, in order to determine what DMN services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within DMN to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

DMN will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on DMN or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DMN; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DMN, or the public.

**Security of your Personal Information**

_Secure SSL_

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

Digital Music News is secured for SSL compliance by RapidSSL.

**COPPA Compliance**

DMN does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from DMN by contacting us here:

Web page: _________________  
Email: _________________  
Phone: _________________

**Changes to this Statement**

DMN will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. DMN encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how DMN is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

DMN welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that DMN has not adhered to this Statement, please contact DMN at:

Digital Music News  
1158 26th street #206  
Santa Monica, California 90403  
Email Address: support@digitalmusicnews.com  
Telephone number: 310.928.1498

Effective as of April 6, 2016
